http://www.gsmd.ac.uk/about_the_school/about_us/policies/privacy_notices/

Home
Back
Menu
GUILDHALL SCHOOL
AboutAbout usJob vacanciesAdministrative structureHistoryCulture MileCity of LondonCorporate documentationEquality DutyEmployability statementPoliciesPrivacy NoticesWebsite Privacy NoticeDisabilityStudent support statementQuality AssuranceBarbican ResidentsSustainabilityHire Guildhall musiciansHire our facilitiesMilton CourtResearchGuildhall InnovationAlumniGraduationStaffTerm datesOpen DaysPress AreaVisiting usContact usMusicDramaProduction ArtsYouth & Adult LearningSupport the School
Apply
Auditions
Prospectus
Open Days
About usJob vacanciesAdministrative structureHistoryCulture MileCity of LondonCorporate documentationEquality DutyEmployability statementPoliciesPrivacy NoticesWebsite Privacy NoticeDisabilityStudent support statementQuality AssuranceBarbican ResidentsSustainabilityHire Guildhall musiciansHire our facilitiesMilton CourtResearchGuildhall InnovationAlumniGraduationStaffTerm datesOpen DaysPress AreaVisiting usContact us
How To ApplyFees And FundingLife At The SchoolInternationalAccess and ParticipationShort CoursesRequest a ProspectusChat to GuildhallView all programmes
Discover Guildhall
Tour the School
Walk the School with Guildhall students
During my time here, I organised an international conference based around my subject involving delegates from 4 continents
Emily Baines
DMus, ‘Mechanical Musical Instruments as a Source for Historical Performance’
The research community at Guildhall is a really interesting place to be
Stefania Donini
PhD
I found it very beneficial to take a break from a busy teaching career to think and reflect on my teaching value, principle and strategies
Yushan Li
PGCert Performance Teaching
Studying at Guildhall is really cool because you are in a setting where the arts are valued by an entire community
Natasha Mbwana
BA Performance & Creative Enterprise
The projects we work on are real - we are in effect constantly getting work experience
Laurie Lumley
BA Video Design for Live Performance
Guildhall is an institution that knows it has to be connected to the outside world - that's the key thing. It's not a bubble. It has roots in the city and in the world.
Jonathan Ferrucci
Artist Diploma Piano
One minute you could be playing in the Guildhall Studio Orchestra with jazz musicians, the next you could be playing in the opera pit, then the next minute you'll be with actors doing the musical and then playing a symphony in the orchestra.
Millie Ashton
BMus Violin
I had access to people I would never have been able to meet as a young composer starting out.
Na'ama Zisser
Doctoral Composer in Residence
I knew about the fantastic tutoring and resources, but the friendly and stimulating environment clinched it for me.
Eden Lonsdale
BMus Composition
I had the opportunity to play percussion with the Guildhall Studio Orchestra which gave me the chance to learn from, and play alongside, amazing senior players, as well as to perform with the incredible Liane Carroll.
Dave Adsett
BMus Jazz Drums
At Guildhall, they don't hold your hand, but they're going to push you to become the actor that you want to be.
Daniel Adeosun
BA Acting
It's the scale of productions that really makes Guildhall stand out. It gets to the point where you think, wow, this is massive. In other places, you just wouldn't have that opportunity to learn on the job.
Sian Clare
BA Technical Theatre Arts (Costume)
Latest News
What's On
Home > About the School > About us > Policies > Privacy Notices
Privacy NoticesHow we use your data
The Guildhall School is a department of the City of London Corporation (“the City of London”) and the City of London is the data controller. The City of London’s privacy notice which explains how the City uses your data can be found at www.cityoflondon.gov.uk/privacy
Contact: Comptroller and City Solicitor, Michael Cogher, at information.officer@cityoflondon.gov.uk
However, where there are activities unique to the Guildhall School these are covered in more detail by the School’s Privacy Notice PNGS18.1 and by privacy notices specific to the area of activity (see below).
If you have any general concerns or questions about how the School looks after your personal information please contact the Secretary and Dean of Students (currently Katharine Lewis) at: registry@gsmd.ac.uk.
If you have a concern or query related to a specific area of activity please contact the relevant department below:
Advancement Privacy Notice PNA18.1 (PDF)Advancement Record Retention RRA18.2 (PDF)Contact for Advancement: Data Manager development@gsmd.ac.uk
Centre for Young Musicians & London Schools Symphony Orchestra Privacy Notice PNCYM18.1 (PDF) CYM & LSSO Record Retention (under development)CYM website Privacy Notice PNWCYM18.1 (PDF)Centre for Young Musicians Taunton Website Privacy Notice PNWCYMT18.1 (PDF)Center for Young Musicians Saffron Website Privacy Notice PNWSCYM18.1 (PDF)Contact for Centre for Young Musicians: ELewis@cym.org.uk
Enterprise, Knowledge Exchange & Research Events Privacy Notice PNEK18.1 (PDF)Enterprise, Knowledge Exchange & Research Events Record Retention RREK18.1 (PDF)Contact for Enterprise, Knowledge Exchange & Research: Innovation Coordinator enterprise@gsmd.ac.uk
External professionals and freelancers (including External Examiners) Privacy Notice PNEP18.1 (PDF)External professsional and freelancers Record Retention (under development)Contact for External Professionals: Secretary & Dean of Students registry@gsmd.ac.uk
Higher Education Student Privacy Notice PNHE18.1 (PDF)Higher Education Record Retention RRHE18.1 (PDF)Contact for Higher Education: Secretary & Dean of Students registry@gsmd.ac.uk
Junior Guildhall Privacy Notice PNJG18.1 (PDF)Junior Guildhall Student Record Retention RRJG18.1 student (PDF)Junior Guildhall Staff Record Retention RRJG18.1 staff (PDF)Contact for Junior Guildhall: Christopher.Poon@gsmd.ac.uk
Research Participants Privacy Policy PNRP18.1 (PDF)Retention requirements for each research project may vary.  Usually a retention period of 7 years beyond the life of the project will apply, but research participants will be informed of the retention schedule prior to participation in a project. Contact for Research: Research Coordinator research@gsmd.ac.uk
Guildhall School Website Privacy Notice PNWS18.1 (PDF)Contact for website: Digital Marketing Manager marketing@gsmd.ac.uk
